{
    "id": "4391709fa2984b04817afaaa3b8f51a3",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Perhaps some gifted persons can ……………………. the future.",
            "description": "Foretell can mean predict.",
            "answers": [
                "foretell",
                "foresight",
                "forestall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9b96d15793b4e749fc5ba51c9304de5"
        },
        {
            "question": "One needs …………………………… to stay within the future.",
            "description": "Foresight can mean forethought.",
            "answers": [
                "foresight",
                "forethought",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "827b43b72ae14b4091ab2330da51ede1"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the …………………….. the author states his intentions in writing the book.",
            "description": "Foreword means introduction.",
            "answers": [
                "foreword",
                "forword",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc16e4e840054e65a38716f4ef8cc3c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Because of other expenses, I will have to …………………………. that new suit.",
            "description": "Forgo means give up.",
            "answers": [
                "forgo",
                "forge",
                "forage"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ff073210de9445ca7d737d25da4a162"
        },
        {
            "question": "She had a ………………………….. that the trip would end in disaster.",
            "description": "Foreboding means premonition.",
            "answers": [
                "forboding",
                "foreboding",
                "forbidding"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67810c9e74424939946bdeefaac56a26"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I saw that ………………………….. bulldog, I went no farther.",
            "description": "Forbidding can mean unfriendly or unapproachable.",
            "answers": [
                "foreboding",
                "forbidding",
                "forbidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d65a04dcc804ab09d09ad896c45a738"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do the cattle have enough ……………………..?",
            "description": "Forage can mean fodder.",
            "answers": [
                "forge",
                "forage",
                "forgo"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45ca248210b84217b08966bed0021c5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did his best to ………………………… a quarrel between the brothers.",
            "description": "Foment means stir up.",
            "answers": [
                "foment",
                "ferment",
                "fomant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e282b9ff11e4d21b843f5a1a8fe9d9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flag …………………………. from the top of the staff.",
            "description": "Flutter can mean wave.",
            "answers": [
                "flustered",
                "fluttered",
                "foistered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76ab710c0494420f8ca94984764e85a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… her diamond necklace.",
            "description": "To flaunt is to make a gaudy display of something.",
            "answers": [
                "flouted",
                "floated",
                "flaunted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9712b748f64046a6b249249408a0fa0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t ……………………… the rules or you will be kicked out of the school.",
            "description": "To flout is to defy.",
            "answers": [
                "flaunt",
                "flout",
                "float"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e5cd68a27c84ff3ab91690660d5cee8"
        },
        {
            "question": "A …………………………… of ducks passed overhead.",
            "description": "Flight is the word used to refer to a group of birds.",
            "answers": [
                "fleet",
                "flight",
                "gang"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e332dd5240f4e90adf21c79bad87856"
        }
    ]
}